Guide to the Cornell Law School Dean's Office records,1888-1989.
Cornell Law School Dean's Office records, 1888-1989
- Inventory of Non-Student Files of Law School
  - Law Revision, Federal (Box 10)
  - Law School, Heeds of (Box 10)
  - Law School Association, Committees on Bar Admission (Box 10)
  - Lawson, Dean John D. (Box 10)
  - Lawyer's Cooperative Publishing Co. (Box 10)
  - Lawyer's Institute (Box 10)
  - League of Nations Conference (Box 10)
  - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association (Box 10)
  - Law Teachers Load (Box 10)
  - LeBoeuf, Randall Jr. (Box 10)
  - Lecturers, Proposed (Box 10)
  - Lee, Henry M. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Lee-Higginson CO. (l item) (Box 10)
  - Lees, Hon. Edward (Box 10)
  - Legal Aid Society (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Legal Ethics (Box 10)
  - Lehman, Herbert (Box 10)
  - Lehigh Valley R.R.C. (1 item) (Box 10)
  - Leidy, Paul A (Box 10)
  - Lemann, Monte (Box 10)
  - Lepaulle, M. Pierre (Box 10)
  - Letchworth, E.H. (Box 10)
  - Letters to Libraries re Law Quarterly (Box 10)
  - Leopold- Schepp Foundation (Box 10)
  - Levison, Isaac (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Lewis, George F. (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Lewis, William Draper (Box 10)
  - Lexapedia Publishing co. (Box 10)
  - Library Accessions (Box 10)
  - Library Expense Account (Box 10)
  - Library Consolidation (Box 11)
  - Library Council (Box 11)
  - Lichtenstein, W.G. (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Little, Brown & Co. (Box 11)
  - Livingston, Henry W. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Llewellyn, Prof. Carl 7. (Box 11)
  - Loewy, Bennc Estate ( 5 pages) (Box 11)
  - Loftus, Edwin (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Lowell, President A. Lawerence (5 items) (Box 11)
  - Lyman, Sobert W. ( 3 items) (Box 11)
  - Lyon, Newell (Box 11)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Mack, William (6 items) (Box 11)
  - Magill, Prof. Roswell (Box 11)
  - Maggs, Douglas B. (prof.) (Box 11)
  - Magrath, J.W. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Magruder, Prof. Calvert (Box 11)
  - Make-up Examinations (Box 11)
  - Major, Cedric A. (Box 11)
  - Mann, Dean A.E. (and Provost- 2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Marcham, Prof. F.G. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Marcus, A.G. (Box 11)
  - Marlowe, Richard ( 2 items) (Box 11)
  - Marshall, Hon. A.W. (Box 11)
  - Marshall, Edwin J. (Box 11)
  - Martin, Paris (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Mason, Herbert D. (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Mc Bain, Prof. J. P. (Box 11)
  - Mc Caskill, Prof. O.L. (Box 11)
  - Mc Clain, Hon EMLIH ( 4 items) (Box 11)
  - McClelland, J.W. (l item) (Box 11)
  - McDonald, William L. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - McGoveny, Prof. D. O. (Box 11)
  - McKeehan, H.H. (6 items) (Box 11)
  - McKenna, Joseph. (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Mackenzie, President A. Stanley (of Dalhousie Univ.) (Box 11)
  - McKinney, William M. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - McKinney, Prize (Box 11)
  - Me Kusick, Dean Marshall (Univ. of S. D.) 2 items (Box 11)
  - Meaney, Alien D. (Box 11)
  - Medical Dept. (Box 11)
  - Medina Law Course (Box 11)
  - Meek, Prof. H.B. (Box 11)
  - Memorial to Court of Appeals. (Box 11)
  - Merril, Prof, Maurice H. (Box 11)
  - Merritt, Dean Ernest (l item) (Box 11)
  - Mersereau, George J. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Messenger Lectures (Box 11)
  - Michie Company (Law Publishers) (Box 11)
  - Micou, Cresswell (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Mikell, Dean William E. (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Miller, Nathan L. (2 folders.) (Box 11)
  - Miller, Walter L. (Box 11)
  - Millener, John A. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Mills, Charles E. (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Mining and Irrigation Law (l item) (Box 11)
  - Minnesota, Univ, of (Box 11)
  - Mintz, Lawerence, and Nelson Mintz (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Mitchell, Percy vonG. (5 items) (Box 11)
  - Mix, Jay P. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Moore, Charles C. (Box 11)
  - Moore, E.R. Company (l item) (Box 11)
  - Moore, Underbill (Box 11)
  - Moot Court (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Morehouse, D.Page Jr. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Moreland, Hon. Sherman (5 items) (Box 11)
  - Morgan, William O. (5 items) (Box 11)
  - Mosher, Judge Edgar S. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Mott, John E. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Mugan Prof. M. D. (items) (Box 11)
  - Mulvaney, Mrs. Laura (Box 11)
  - Murphy, Gleeson (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Myron Taylor Hall (Box 11)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - National Bankruptcy Law List (l item) (Box 11)
  - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement (Box 11)
  - National Conference of Bar Examiners (Box 11)
  - National Jr. Bar Association (Box 11)
  - National Life Insurance Co. (G.B. Young) (Box 11)
  - National Youth Administration - Student Aid- Univ. Placement Bureau (Box 11)
  - National Mercantile Agency (2 items) (Box 11)
  - National Sportsman (l item) (Box 11)
  - Naval Training School (Box 11)
  - Nebekerk Frank K. (Box 11)
  - Needs of the Law School (Box 11)
  - Newark Law School (Box 11)
  - New York County Lawyer's Association (Box 11)
  - New York Court of Appeals (Box 11)
  - New York Law Journal (Box 11)
  - New York Sun (2 items) (Box 11)
  - New York Telephone Co. (Box 11)
  - New York State Association of Judges at Children's Courts (Box 11)
  - New York State Bar Meeting (Ithaca) (Box 11)
  - New York State Board of Law Examiners 1923-1935 (Box 11)
  - New York State Conference on Legal Education (Box 11)
  - Nicholls, Col. J.C. (Box 11)
  - Nichols, Dean E.L. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Nofer, Edward J. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - Non-Resident Lectures, Committee on (Box 11)
  - Norris, Prof. H.H. (l item) (Box 11)
  - Northrup, Prof. E.J. (6 items) (Box 11)
  - Notestein, Prof. Wallace (Box 11)
  - Noyes, Hon. Walter C. (3 items) (Box 11)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - 0 'Brian, J.E. (Box 11)
  - O'Gorman, Hon. J.A. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Oliphant, Hermann, Hon. (Box 11)
  - Olney, Peter (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Orth Chair (Box 11)
  - Orton, Jesse F. (Box 11)
  - Ostorn, Albert S. (Box 11)
  - Oshorne, Hon. James W. (Box 11)
  - "0" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Page, Prof. S.E. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Page, Prof. W.H. (Box 11)
  - Paine, David (Box 11)
  - Palmer, Archie M. (Box 11)
  - Parks, Prof. James L. (4 items) (Box 11)
  - Parrott, Carolyn C. (Box 11)
  - Parsell, Dr. Charles V. (Box 11)
  - Parsons, Russell C. (2 items) (Box 11)
  - Patterson, Woodford (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Paul, Randolph P. (Box 12)
  - Pennsylvania Board of Law Examiners (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Pension Fund Committee (Box 12)
  - Peters, Provost H.W. (Box 12)
  - Peters, Norman W. (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Pfann, George (Box 12)
  - Phelps, Prof. B. J. (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Phi Alpha Delta (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Phi Delta Phi (Box 12)
  - Phi Kappa Phi (Box 12)
  - Phi Kappa Phi (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Capt. E.L. (1 items) (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Dr. E.W. (1 item) (Box 12)
  - Phillips, Percy W. (Box 12)
  - Pillsbury, Warren (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Politis, Prof. N. (Box 12)
  - Poole, Franklin 0. (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Post War International Problems (Box 12)
  - Pound, Judge Cuthbert 77. (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Pound, Dean Roscoe (Box 12)
  - Powell, Richard B. (Box 12)
  - Powell, Prof. Thomas R. (Box 12)
  - Powers, Lawerence J. (Box 12)
  - Price, Guernsey (Box 12)
  - Pritchett, Dr. Henry S. (Box 12)
  - Professorship Fund ( Temporary) (Box 12)
  - Psychiatry (l item) (Box 12)
  - Public Information (Box 12)
  - Putnam, Hon. Harrington (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Purchasing Department (Box 12)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Qualifing Certificates (Box 12)
  - "Q," Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Radford, E. B. and Co. (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Band, William Jr. (Box 12)
  - Ransom, William (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Ratcliffe, S.K. (Box 12)
  - Raye-Smith, Mrs. Eugenie (4 items) (Box 12)
  - Reath, Thomas (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Records of Students (Box 12)
  - Reese, Fred S. (Box 12)
  - Registration Figures (Box 12)
  - Reyna, Juan (Box 12)
  - Reynolds, Robert P. (l item) (Box 12)
  - Richards, Harry (of Gimbel Brothers - 3 items) (Box 12)
  - Richards, Deen H.S. (Univ. Of Wise.) (Box 12)
  - Richter, Prof. A. .Richtmeyer, Prof. F.K: (Box 12)
  - Riesman, David Jr. (Box 12)
  - Riggins, Glenn (3 items) (Box 12)
  - Hitter, Gilbert P. (7 items) (Box 12)
  - Robinson, Prof. James J. (Box 12)
  - Rogalsky, George F. (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Rogers, Hon. Henry Wade (Box 12)
  - Root, Elihu (Box 12)
  - Bosbroolt, F.E. (Box 12)
  - Ross, Miss Helen M. (1 item) (Box 12)
  - Rowell, Newton (Box 12)
  - Rowlee, Prof. W.W. (2 items) (Box 12)
  - Russian Civilization "R" Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Sackett, Henry W. (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Salaries of Law Librarians (Box 13)
  - Sanderson, James Gardner (Box 13)
  - Saperston, Alfred M. (Box 13)
  - Schedules of Hours for Exams (Box 13)
  - Schedules of Examinations (Box 13)
  - Schedules of the Law School (Box 13)
  - Schenck, William E. (Box 13)
  - Schiff Lecturship (Box 13)
  - Schuebly, Merrill I. (Box 13)
  - Schurman, President Jacob Gould (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Schuylkill, Legal Record (l item) (Box 13)
  - Scott, Dean Austin (Univ. of Iowa - 2 items) (folder #2 of Harvard) (Box 13)
  - Scott, Hon. James Brown (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Seavey, Warren A. (Box 13)
  - Securities Act, Pa. Law (Box 13)
  - Senior, John L. (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Shapiro, Joseph (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Shearn, Clarence J. (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Shearer, Prof. John S. (Box 13)
  - Shelley, Leander (Box 13)
  - Shepardson, Whitney (Box 13)
  - Shepard, Frederick, (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Shurter, Prof, E,D. (Box 13)
  - Sickmon, Hon. May C. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Sigma Nu Scholarship Committee (l item) (Box 13)
  - Simmnton, James W. (Box 13)
  - Simpson, Harold E. (Box 13)
  - Simpeon, Prof. Smith (Box 13)
  - Skinner, Edward M. (Box 13)
  - Skinner, Fred (l item) (Box 13)
  - deSloovere, Frederick J. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Gov. Alfred (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Acting President A.W. (Box 13)
  - Smith, George C. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Herbert A. (7 items) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Young B. (Box 13)
  - Smithers, William W. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Snyder, W.W. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Solovay, Benjamin (l item) (Box 13)
  - Speakers (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Spense, W. J. (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Spencer, Arthur W. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Sprague, George C. (Registrar of NYU - 2 items) (Box 13)
  - Sprigg, Edward (Supt. of Buildings - 2 items) (Box 13)
  - Squires, Dr. Paul C. (Box 13)
  - Stafford, John (l item) (Box 13)
  - Stagg, Hon C. Tracy (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Stalter, Charles Cooper (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Standard College of Law (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Stanton, Theodore (7 items) (Box 13)
  - State Board of Law Examiners (New York) (Box 13)
  - Statistics Regarding Students (Box 13)
  - Stevens, E.L. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Stevens, Prof, Robert S. (Box 13)
  - Stone, Dean Harlan Fiske (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Storms, William H. (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Strawn, Silas (Box 13)
  - Strunk, Prof. W. Jr. (l items) (Box 13)
  - Student Affairs Committee (Box 13)
  - Student Petitions (Box 13)
  - Student Conduct (Box 13)
  - Committee on Student Rooms, Myron Taylor Hall (Box 13)
  - Suggett, Hon. John W (Box 13)
  - Sundheimer, Malcolm (l item) (Box 13)
  - Swartwood, Hon. Charles B. (3 items) (Box 13)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Taft; William Howard (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Tansey, George J. (Box 13)
  - Tarbell, Clarence D. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Taylor, Hon. Harry L. (Box 13)
  - Taylor and Thurber (l item) (Box 13)
  - Teaching Fellow (Box 13)
  - Terwilliger, Robert E. (Box 13)
  - Texas Bar and Supreme Court (Box 13)
  - Thayer, Dean Ezra (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Thilly, Dean Frank (Box 13)
  - Thomas, Hiram (3 items) (Box 13)
  - Thomason, L.R. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Thompson, Edward Co. (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Thompson, C.W. (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Thorp, Charles M. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Thorpe, Prof. Francis N. (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Thurber, Raymond D. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Thurston, Edward J. (8 items) (Box 13)
  - Tibbetts, Harland B. (Box 13)
  - Tiernan, Prof. J.P. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Tobey, Harry (3 Item) (Box 13)
  - Tobey, Waldo (Box 13)
  - Tombo, Prof. Rudolph Jr. (1 item) (Box 13)
  - Townsend, Howard C. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Traviesc, Martin (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Treasurer of Univ. o (Box 13)
  - Treman, Alien H. (Box 13)
  - Treman, Charles (l item) (Box 13)
  - Treman, King and Co, (l item) (Box 13)
  - Treman, Robert E. (Box 13)
  - Treman, Robert H. (Box 13)
  - Trickett, Dean William (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Trimble, Charles E. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Trousdale, J.B. (Box 13)
  - Trow, H. C. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Trustees, Board of 1924-1939 (Box 13)
  - Tschida, M. (2 items) (Box 13)
  - Tuition Increase - 1912 (Box 13)
  - Turner, Dr. J.H. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Tutchings, Harvey (4 items) (Box 13)
  - Tattle, Elbert P. (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - "T" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - University Policy (Box 13)
  - Updegraff, Clarence (Box 13)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Vance, William R. (Box 13)
  - Van Cleef, Myderse (Box 13)
  - Vanderlyn Diary (re) (l item) (Box 13)
  - Van Eysiuga, Prof. (Box 13)
  - Van Hecke, Prof. H.T. (Box 13)
  - Van Kirk, Mr. L. H. (l item) (Box 13)
  - Van Schaick, George (Box 13)
  - Vedder, Earl C. (Box 13)
  - Verrell, Prof. Harold (Box 13)
  - Veterens (Box 13)
  - Von Moschciskev, Hon. Robert (Box 13)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Van Vleck, William R. (Box 14)
  - Wadhams, Frederick E. (Box 14)
  - Wait, J. C. (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Wakeley, Arthur C. (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Walker, Jones Blaine Jr. (Box 14)
  - Walters, J. Henry (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Walz, Dean William (3 items) (Box 14)
  - War Course (Box 14)
  - Warner, Glenn S. (l item) (Box 14)
  - Warren, Edward H. (Box 14)
  - Washington D.C. Law Club (Box 14)
  - Washington, George (Box 14)
  - Watkins, Thomas D. (l item) (Box 14)
  - Watson, Archibald (Box 14)
  - Webb, Edwin (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Weld, Prof. H.P. (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Wells, Prof. George F. (l item) (Box 14)
  - Werner, Hon. Willian E. (Box 14)
  - West Publishing Co. (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Wheeler, Everett P. (Box 14)
  - Whipple, Prof. G.M. (l item) (Box 14)
  - White, Andrew D. (l item) (Box 14)
  - White, J. Du Pratt (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - White, W. B. (l item) (Box 14)
  - Whittaker, Prof. B.E. (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Wicker sham, George (Box 14)
  - Wickersham, Cornelius (Box 14)
  - Wickham, Robert S. (Box 14)
  - Wickser, Phillip JW ( of State Board of Examiners) (Box 14)
  - Wigmore, John H. (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Wiley, George (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Wilkinson, Albert E. (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Willcox, Walter F. (Box 14)
  - Willever, E.E. (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Willever, Fund (Box 14)
  - Williams, Carl (Box 14)
  - Williams, H.E. (l item) (Box 14)
  - Williams, Prof. J.K. (2 items) (Box 14)
  - Williams, Miss Louise H. (4 items) (Box 14)
  - Williams, Wordsworth, B. (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Williamson law Book Co. (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Williston, Samuel (Box 14)
  - Wilmot, F.M. (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Wilson, C.W. Jr. (5 items) (Box 14)
  - Wilson, Lyman P. (Box 14)
  - Wilson, Wilfred M. (3 items?) (Box 14)
  - Wilson W.W. (6 items) (Box 14)
  - Wolkinson, Hermann (Box 14)
  - Woodruff, Prof. Edwin H. (Box 14)
  - Woodward, Prof. Fred C. (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - World Peace Foundation (Box 14)
  - Wormser, Prof. I. Maurice (3 items) (Box 14)
  - Wright, Nathaniel (2 items) (Box 14)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Yorkey, Daniel G. (Box 14)
  - Young, Prof. C, Y.P. (Box 14)
  - "Y" Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Zeigler, Prof. E.A. (2 items) (Box 14)